Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series, 1880-1920: Preliminary Finding Aid AC317
University Archives
- Buildings and Grounds, 1811-1944; 71 boxes
  - Eating Clubs, 1899-1923; 12 boxes
    - Quadrangle, old building, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 511
    - Quadrangle Club in Fine House, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 512
    - Terrace Club, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 519-520
    - Group flashlight at Gateway Club, Feb., 1919., 1 box (Box 31)
      Original sleeve No. 94. Same as plate 625 except Harold Wanless.
      Plate number: 626
    - Group picture at Gateway Club, Spring of 1919, 1 box (Box 31)
      Original sleeve No. 95
      Plate number: 627
    - Group flashlight at Gateway Club, Feb., 1919., 1 box (Box 31)
      Original sleeve No. 93. Top, left to right: Jim Armstrong, Bill Kloppenburg, Tom Hargest, Charles Ringwald, Walter Stewart, Artie Horton, Middle: Harold Wanless, John Worley, Bobby Porteous, Maury Clark, Dick Hartshorne, Bottom: Rudy Cannon, Maury Rogers, Sam Dodd, Mac Harper and Prentice Dean.
      Plate number: 625
    - Terrace Club new building uner construction, 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 137
      Plate number: 668
    - Tower Club, 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 138
      Plate number: 669
    - Gateway Club, front view, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 131
      Plate number: 662
    - Gateway Club, rear view, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 132
      Plate number: 663
    - Pool room, Gateway Club, spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 133
      Plate number: 664
    - Living room, Gateway Club, 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 134
      Plate number: 665
    - Private dining room, Gateway Club, 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 135
      Plate number: 666
    - Dining room, Gateway Club, 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 136
      Plate number: 667
    - Japanese cherry tree at Gateway Club, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 440
      Plate number: 935
    - Group at time of Gateway House Party, 1923, 1 box (Box 54)
      Original sleeve No. 660. With Bill Rogers, Kay Jarvis, Libby Schaffner, Sprague, Mr. and Mrs. Dugan, Priscilla and Kenneth, Mr. and Mrs. Jarvis, and Fred Milligan
      Plate number: 1013
    - Group at time of Gateway House Party, 1924, 1923; 1 box (Box 54)
      Original sleeve No. 661. With Bill Rogers, Kay Jarvis, Libby Schaffner, Sprague, Mr. and Mrs. Dugan, Priscilla and Kenneth, Mr. and Mrs. Jarvis, Fred Milligan, and H.R.W.
      Plate number: 1014
    - Henry and Louise, Steward and cook of Gateway Club, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1072
      Plate number: 1078
    - Gateway Club bunch at Pyne Estate, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1075
      Plate number: 1081
    - Gateway Club reunion, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1076
      Plate number: 1082
    - 1920 section of Gateway Club, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1077
      Plate number: 1083
    - Members of Gateway Club, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1078
      Plate number: 1084
    - Members of Gateway Club, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1079
      Plate number: 1085
  - Faculty Housing, 1916-1926; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show faculty housing.
    - Faculty housing, 101 Broadmead being built, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 125
    - Broadmead and Fitzrandolph houses being built, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 192-193
  - Fitzrandolph Gate, 1916-1926; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show views of Fitzrandolph Gate.
    - Fitzrandolph Gate, under construction, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 126
    - Fitzrandolph Gate, cupola Nassau Hall in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 127
    - Fitzrandolph Gate, with horse and buggy, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 439
    - Buildings and grounds, Fitz-Randolph gates at night, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1256
  - General, 1892-1922; 15 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Princeton University buildings and grounds. These plates could not clearly be associated with other topics in this series.
    - First Presbyterian Church with Maclean House, Nassau Hall cupola and Alexander Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 128
    - Fitzpatrick Field House, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 201
    - Frick Lab, north and west facades, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 202
    - Tuscullum, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 228
    - 79 Hall, west facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 226
    - Jones Hall Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 211
    - Laughlin, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 212-213
    - Plaque, entry in memory of William Wolcott Fisk, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 236
    - Plaque, 1922, Fairview, 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 237
    - Ferris Thompson wall from southeast corner, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 279
    - A plan for the architectural and topigraphical development of Princeton University, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 14, Box 15)
      Plate number: 301-303
    - Dickinson Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 380
    - Brown, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 406
    - Dickinson, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 432
    - DOD, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 434
    - Drumthwacket Lake, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 435
    - Edwards, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 436
    - Field House, 1892, 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 438
    - Foulke, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 440
    - Golf Course, inn in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 441
    - Henry, just finished no landscaping, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 448
    - Hill Dormitory, R.R. station in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 449
    - Incubator, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 458
    - Infirmary, old building, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 459
    - McCarter, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 468
    - Third World Center, Osbourne Club House with wood fence, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 521
    - West College, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 528
    - Architect's drawing of Princeton battle monument, Undated; 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 400
      Plate number: 895
    - Through the arch of the library court, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 430
      Plate number: 925
    - The library from the coroner of old chapel, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 439
      Plate number: 934
    - Tigers at gate between Blair and Little Halls, Undated; 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 482
      Plate number: 984
    - Niche inside library court, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1070
      Plate number: 1076
  - Graduate College, 1916-1926; 13 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show views of the Graduate College.
    - Graduate College, from Brokaw Hall at Seminary with tennis court in foreground, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 129
    - Graduate College, Cleveland Tower from inside court, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 130
    - Graduate College from golf course, pre 1926, circa 1926; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 203
    - Graduate College, Cleveland Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 204-205
    - Graduate College, Cleveland Tower from Rose Garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 206
    - Graduate College, Cleveland Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 280
    - Graduate College, Cleveland Tower with east and south facades, circa 1920; 1 box (Box 15)
      Plate number: 307
    - Graduate College from golf course with refelction in pond, Before 1926; 1 box (Box 15)
      Plate number: 308
    - Graduate College, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 569-581
    - Graduate College from west, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 582-583
    - Graduate College, Cleveland Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 584-587
    - Graduate College with reflection, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 588-589
    - Graduate College with Wyman House and water tank, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 590
    - Graduate College, Procter Hall, west window, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 591
    - Graduate College, Procter Hall, toward organ, Undated; 1 box (Box 29)
      Plate number: 592
    - Statuette of Venus de Milo in Grad. College niche, May, 1921, 1 box (Box 34)
      Original sleeve No. 154
      Plate number: 686
    - Graduate College at sunset time from golf links, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 470. (Pic. cover)
      Plate number: 937
    - Procter Hall, Grad. Coll., 1918, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 460
      Plate number: 956
    - Tower of Graduate College, 1918, 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 461
      Plate number: 957
    - Terrace of Graduate College, 1919, 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 462
      Plate number: 958
    - Graduate College reflected in Lake Listerine 1919, 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 463. (vertical)
      Plate number: 959
    - Graduate College reflected in Lake Listerine 1919, 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 464. (horizontal)
      Plate number: 960
    - Graduate College from some distance down the road toward seminary, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 465. (horizontal)
      Plate number: 961
    - Graduate College approach from raod, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 466. (vertical)
      Plate number: 962
    - Graduate College from the west, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 468
      Plate number: 964
    - Interior of Graduate College court, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 469
      Plate number: 965
    - North side of Graduate College when wisteria is in bloom, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 472
      Plate number: 975
    - Wisteria bush at north side of Graduate College, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 473
      Plate number: 976
    - Graduate college from behind Dean's garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 467
      Plate number: 963
    - Dean's garden, Grad. Col., June 1923, 1 box (Box 51)
      Plate number: 966
    - Vertical view of Cleveland Tower from golf links, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Original sleeve No. 471
      Plate number: 974
    - Cleveland Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 51)
      Plate number: 972
    - Graduate College at sunset, Undated; 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 475. (Horizontal)
      Plate number: 977
    - Graduate College at sunset, Undated; 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 476
      Plate number: 978
    - Statue of Venus de Milo in niche in Graduate College, spring of 1921, 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 477
      Plate number: 979
    - Cleveland Tower from cloister of Graduate College, Undated; 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1064
      Plate number: 1070
    - View from top of Cleveland Tower, 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1123
      Plate number: 1121
    - Graduate College tower, 1916, 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1119
      Plate number: 1117
    - Buildings and grounds, Graduate College, doorway with two alumni on alumni day, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1257
  - Guyot Hall, 1919; 10 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Guyot Hall.
    - Guyot Hall, preparing for construction, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 131
    - Guyot Hall, just finished, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 132
    - Guyot, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 442
    - East end of Guyot Hall in a snow storm, 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 449
      Plate number: 945
    - Guyot Hall Museum, Undated; 1 box (Box 103)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 104)
      4x5
    - Guyot Hall Museum, Undated; 1 box (Box 104)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 4 boxes (Box 105, Box 106, Box 107, Box 108)
      Accession: AR.2001.080
    - Guerilla Skeleton, undated; 1 box
      Glass plates within this series show a guerilla skeleton from six different perspectives.
      - Guerilla Skeleton, full front view, Guyot Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 69)
        Plate number: 1318
      - Guerilla Skeleton, full side view, Guyot Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 69)
      - Guerilla Skeleton, head from below, Guyot Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 69)
        Plate number: 1320
      - Guerilla Skeleton, side view of head, Guyot Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 69)
        Plate number: 1321
      - Guerilla Skeleton, front view of head, Guyot Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 69)
        Plate number: 1322
      - Guerilla Skeleton, full front view, Guyot Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 69)
        Plate number: 1323
  - Gymnasium, 1901-1944; 7 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Princeton University Gymnasium Buildings.
    - Gymnasium swimming pool, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 133
    - Gymnasium 1903-1944 with part of Brokaw memorial, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 134
    - Gymnasium 1903-1944, recently finished, no landscaping, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 135
    - Gymnasium, 1903-1944, architects's rendering, north elevation, Cope & Stewardson, June 5th 1901, 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 158
    - Bonner-Marquand gym, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 191
    - Gymnasium, 1903-43, 1903-1943; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 443
    - Gymnasium, 1903-44, 1903-1944; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 444
    - Gymnasium and Brokaw Memorial, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 445
    - Gym and Brokaw Memorial, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 446
    - Roadway to the gym in the spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 428
      Plate number: 923
    - The gymnasium from the east, 1920, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 429
      Plate number: 924
    - Princeton Gymnasium tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1065
      Plate number: 1071
    - Bonner Gymnasium, Undated; 1 box (Box 111)
      Plate number: 371
  - Hamilton Hall, 1918; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Hamilton Hall.
    - Hamilton Hall from University Place, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 136
    - Plaque, Hamilton Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 238
    - Entrance to Hamilton Hall court, 1928, 1918; 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 394
      Plate number: 889
    - Part of Hamilton Hall from outside, showing room 1D, Undated; 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1068
      Plate number: 1074
  - Holder Hall, 1918; 7 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Holder Hall.
    - Holder Hall and tower, north facade with Madison, circa 1918; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 281
    - Holder Hall, east and north facades, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 282
    - Holder Hall, northeast corner and tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 283
    - Holder Hall, before tower built, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 450
    - Holder Hall, tower from east, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 451
    - Holder Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 452-453, 457
    - Holder Tower, from accross Nassau Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 454
    - Holder Tower, from court with cloisters, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 455
    - Holder Tower, from west with people in park, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 456
    - Hamilton Court and Holder Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 207
    - Holder Tower from accross Nassau Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 208
    - Holder Tower from court, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 209
    - Holder Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 210
    - Hamiltom Court with Holder Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 25)
      Plate number: 447
    - Holder Tower, 1918, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 398
      Plate number: 893
    - Holder cloister from the court, 1918, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 392
      Plate number: 887
    - Holder Hall from east with large willow tree, Undated; 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 418. (Pic. cover)
      Plate number: 913
    - Interior of Holder Court, Undated; 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1121
      Plate number: 1119
  - John C. Green School of Science, 1907-1919; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show the John C. Green School of Science.
    - School of Science (John C. Green), Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 377-379
    - John C. Green School of Science, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 461
    - John C. Green School of Science and Dickinson, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 462
    - John C. Green School of Science and with Dickinson, house in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 463
    - John C. Green School of Science and part of Dickinson, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 464
    - Magnolia tree and School of Science, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 435
      Plate number: 930
    - Magnolia tree and School of Science, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 436
      Plate number: 931
    - The School of Science, Undated; 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1061
      Plate number: 1067
  - Little Hall, 1901; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Little Hall.
    - Architectural rendering, extension of Stafford Little Hall and gymnasium building, 1901; 1 box (Box 5)
      Plate number: 105
    - Little Hall with tiger gate, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 214
    - Little Hall, east facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 15)
      Plate number: 309
    - Little, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 466
    - Little with gate, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 467
  - MaClean House, 1907-1919; 2 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show the President's House, also known as MaClean House.
    - MaClean House, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 138
    - MaClean House, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 476
  - Madison Hall, 1907-1919; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Madison Hall.
    - Madison Hall from west, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 215-216
    - Madison Hall, part of north facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
      Plate number: 287
    - Madison and Holder Tower, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 477
    - Buildings and grounds, Madison under construction - view from Campbell, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1258
    - Buildings and grounds, Madison under construction - view from Campbell, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1259
  - McCosh Hall, 1907-1919; 8 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show McCosh Hall.
    - McCosh Hall, under construction, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 137
    - McCosh Hall and Mather Sundail, circa 1907; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 312
    - McCosh Walk, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 381
    - McCosh Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 469
    - McCosh Hall from west, no Dickenson, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 470
    - McCosh Hall with sundial, no Dickinson, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 471
    - McCosh Hall from north without Dickinson, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 472
    - McCosh Hall from north with sundial, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 473
    - McCosh Walk, gate posts for Prospect on right, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 474
    - McCosh Walk, Prospect gate posts at right, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 475
    - McCosh Walk looking west, 1919, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 412
      Plate number: 907
    - McCosh Walk looking east, 1919, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 413
      Plate number: 908
    - McCosh Hall from near old chapel, 1919, 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 414
      Plate number: 909
    - Mather sun dial, McCosh Hall, 1919, 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 415
      Plate number: 910
    - McCosh Hall from roof of School of Science building, Undated; 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 416
      Plate number: 911
    - McCosh walk in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 458
      Plate number: 954
    - McCosh Walk in winter, 1918, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1062
      Plate number: 1068
  - Memorials, 1811-1900; 5 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show memorial services and structures around the Princeton University campus.
    - Brokaw Memorial, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 113
    - View to south, Brown Brokaw Memorial, circa 1900; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 174
    - Architectural memorial, 1811-1899; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Memorial architecture, Alexander Robert Fordyce, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Memorial John Bright, 1811-1889, Florence Brooks Asten, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
  - Murray Hall, 1900-1920; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Murray Hall.
    - Murray Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 387
    - Murray-Dodge, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 480
    - Murray-Dodge Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 421
      Plate number: 916
  - Nassau Hall, 1900-1920; 9 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Nassau Hall.
    - Nassau Hall, south facade, circa 1900; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 142
    - House of Nassau coat of arms, Undated; 1 box (Box 12)
      Plate number: 284-285
    - Nassau Hall, north facade, 1911-1967, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
      Plate number: 288
    - Nassau Hall tigers, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
      Plate number: 289
    - Plaque, Nassau Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
      Plate number: 290-291
    - Nassau Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 388-389
    - Nassau Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 481-482
    - Nassau Hall, before 1905, 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 483
    - Nassau Hall, before 1905, Before 1906; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 484
    - Nassau Hall Cupola, between Reunion and Stanhope, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 485
    - Nassau Hall Tigers, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 486-487
    - Memorial Hall, Nassau Hall, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 107
      Plate number: 638
    - Side view of Nassau Hall tiger with snow, winter of 1919-20, 1919-1920; 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 401. (Pic cover)
      Plate number: 896
    - Front view of Nassau Hall tiger with snow, winter of 1920, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 402
      Plate number: 897
    - Side view of Nassau Hall tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 403
      Plate number: 898
    - Front view of Nassau Hall tiger, Undated; 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 404
      Plate number: 899
    - Nassau Hall tigers, 1920, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 405
      Plate number: 900
    - Front view of Nassau Hall, 1920, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 406
      Plate number: 901
    - Rear view of Nassau Hall, 1919, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 407
      Plate number: 902
    - Corner of Nassau Hall near library, 1919, 1 box (Box 47)